[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Jesse, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "I'm doing well, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "How re you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "You are looking very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Yes, that's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "How does that work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I will.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "You're basically endorsing a form of fascism, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "We're already fascists, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Why is it just one way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, I guess that -- here's what I thought when I read your book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "How do you actually have a government that works if everyone is an independent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Well, you can still -- you can turn the Democrats and Republicans into special interests, which is what they are anyway.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "These would be independents formerly known as Democrats and Republicans, wouldn't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "No, not necessarily.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "You know why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Go on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "You know why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "When you hear the president and Republican nominee going at it like this, given the state of economy, what's your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, my reaction, it doesn't matter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I think it's awful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "So presumably you'll be boycotting FOX and MSNBC on your book tour, will you, Jesse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I won't be boycotting them.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "-- will have me on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "He has?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Well, he is pulling them out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "He's pulling them out, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, I guess he is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "What would you do with Iran?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Well, I'll give you a scenario.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 370, "question": "So the U.S. -- the U.S. is definitely threatened by these countries in what way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "You don't think --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S.", "U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", ":", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I think that's what -- the defense basically filed that motion today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Is it damaged at all by the fact that quite a few of the boys who are now men obviously have also filed civil complaints, so there is a potential financial incentive here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I don't think it's damaged.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jason Carroll"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Don't they have some right to some recompense to help them deal with the abuse as they go forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I saw when Jason Carroll was talking about the defense strategy, you shaking your head vigorously there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "You clearly don't make a lot of that, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I don't understand what the defense strategy is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "It is classic grooming behaviors, isn't it, we're looking at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What's that all about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I think both sides probably think this is going to advantage them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Why are you running?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Well, I've been in public service just about all of my adult life, in addition to the time my wife and I spent running a small business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "What do you say to those who say, you know, you're no spring chicken and the young guy should get a run?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "WP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Well, that's a good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "What did you think when you heard that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Well, I think he's got a good message there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Arizona"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I think that's the distraction my opponent has tried to use to move us away from what's really important to the people of Arizona.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Just for the purposes of clarification, are you a big supporter of the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Well, when it comes to the November election, I will support the president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]